

# **Gentry Atkinson**

#### Instructor and Researcher

13 January 1984



Austin, TX (713)725-4523



github.com/gentry-atkinson



gma23@txstate.edu

# About me ——

I am a first year PhD student at Texas State University in San Marcos, TX. I have recently returned to school after serving in the US Army. This has given me the opportunity to find my passion for instruction and research. This is my second semester as an instructional assistant but I hope to have many more chances in my future to guide students towards finding their own passion in Computer Science.

# Skills ———

Wireless Communication

Machine Learning

Algorithmic Design

Python

Teamwork

Patience

C++

### Interests

Unsupervised machine learning, municipal data analysis, sensor arrays, pedagogy, instruction, robotics, and bicycling.

## Education

since 2018	Ph.D. student in Computer Science	Texas State University
	Focus in Informatics	

2011-2014 B.Sc. summa cum laude Texas State University

Majoring in Computer Science

2009-2010 A.A.Sc. Portland Community College

Majoring in CIS

#### [Publications]

2014 Musing: Adaptable Mobile Augmented Reality Application for Muse-

ums and Art Galleries

2014 Musing: Interactive Didactics for Art Museums and Galleries via Im-

age Processing and Augmented Reality

2014 Musing - Enhancing Education Experience through a Virtual Museum

Application

#### Awards

2017 Army Commendation2015, 2016 Army Achievement Medals

2014 Texas State Mobile Development Hack-a-thon: Best in Show

## Experience

2018-Now	Doctoral Instructional Assistant	San Marcos, TX
----------	----------------------------------	----------------

2014-2018 Sergeant, US Army Tacoma, WA

2013-2014 Research Assistant San Marcos, TX

2011-2013 Peddicabie Austin, TX

# Other information

#### Volunteer Work

I worked full-time as a volunteer for Americorps in the Washington, DC area for 10 months spanning 2002 and 2003. My duties included leading small teams in park reconstruction and working as a Teacher's Assistant for a third grade class.

I am now a volunteer radio operator with the TCARES emergency radio network.